卢克:好,抓紧了,
Luke: Ok, now hold this down and be careful,
小心点,如果两条线相碰会让你感到强烈的震动.
it those to wires touch you can get a nasty shock.
迈克:本.
Mike: Ben.
本:啊.
Ben: Yow.
迈克:帮我拿一下.
Mike: Hold this down for me.
本:好的,啊.
Ben: Sure, aww.
卢克:成了,好.
Luke: Got it yeah.
迈克:好了,好了,看看.一条线,
Mike: Alright, alright, look at that this one cable,
三个接头,几个频道.看,你是个天才.
three sets different channels, look you are a genius.
本:是我还是这个房间里的人昏了头了?
Ben: Is it just me or does this room taste like thin foil?
麦琪:哦,我太兴奋了,
Maggie: Oh I am so excited I finally get to get away with your father,
终于要和你们父亲出去了.两天美妙的舞会,我们还可以看星星.
two glorious days of dancing and gazing at the stars.
卢克:你是不是把这个老人疗养院写进过你的消费者专栏里了?
Luke: I thought you were reviewing this old folks resort for your consumer
column?
迈克:是的,你为什么要把爸爸拖着去陪你呢?
Mike: Yeah and why are you dragging dad along mom?
麦琪:那不是什么老人疗养院,
Maggie: It is not an old folks resort and I know your father is just excited
我知道你爸爸跟我一样的兴奋.
as I am.
杰森:有人诽谤了我,把我的痛苦带走了.
Jason: Somebody just cover me with dirt and put me out of my misery.
麦琪:杰森,快点把东西整理好,
Maggie: Jason, let's just finish getting you packed and we'll talk about
我们在去卡斯科斯的路上还要谈谈呢.
it on the way to The Cascos.
杰森:啊,这个周末我们不去老人疗养院了,是吗?
Jason: Ah this isn't the weekend for that old folks resort is it?
麦琪:杰森,那不是什么老人疗养院,他们接待超过40岁的人.
Maggie: Jason, it is not an old folks resort they cater to the over forty class.
迈克:决定了,妈妈?
Mike: Well make up your mind mom?
麦琪:杰森,他们说,
Maggie: Jason, they said if we get there early enough they will give us
如果我们早点去的话,会给我们一套蜜月套房.
one of their honey moon suites.
杰森:老人疗养院里也有蜜月套房吗?
Jason: They have honeymoon suites at the old folks place?
他们还免费送你新婚酒吗?
Will they give you a complimentary magnum of jherritoe?
亲爱的,对不起,我只是太累了,我连走路都困难.
Honey I'm sorry it's just that I'm so tired I can hardly to...walk this road.
麦琪:我帮你打包.
Maggie: I help you pack.
杰森:我要去看电视.
Jason: I'm going to watching TV.
迈克:爸爸,爸爸,听我说,开萝尔去学校了,是吗?
Mike: Dad, dad, listen this.Carol's going to school right?
克莉丝要去亨德森家过周末,而我和卢克,
Chrissy is going to the Henderson's for the weekend and Luke,
本要在沙发上待两天,
Ben and I are going to live on this couch for two days of non-stop
看连续播放的体育节目,吃克莉丝喜欢的食物,
sports, Chrissy's food and
还要互相敲打脑壳.
all around knuckle head guy stuff.
杰森:互相敲打脑壳?
Jason: Knuckle head guy stuff?
迈克:爸爸,你俩不能陪我们了.
Mike: Dad, you two guys can't stay with us,
我是说,我们的这个周末注定是完美的.
I mean nothing can ruin this perfect weekend.
开萝尔:嗨.
Carol: Hello.
迈克:啊,开萝尔,你在这干什么?
Mike: Aw, Carol, what are you doing here?
开萝尔:佛兰斯使用烫发钳不小心把宿舍点着了.
Carol: France had fire to her dorm room with her butane curling iron.
本:好了,我弄了土豆片,牛肉干,
Ben: Alright I got chips, slim jims, pork ranch and spray cheese,
熏猪肉和奶酪.啊,你在这里干什么?
aw what are you doing here?
麦琪:好了,杰森,
Maggie: Ok Jason I left your suitcase open upstairs just throw on your
你的行李箱在楼上,把你跳舞用的鞋扔进去,我们就走吧.
dancing shoes and let's go.
杰森:亲爱的,只是假设地说一下,
Jason: Honey, just hypothetically speaking what do you think will happen
如果我说这个周末真的不想跟你一起去,你会怎么样?
if I said I don't really want to go with you this weekend?
麦琪:假设地说一下,我们可以在地下室摆一张床.
Maggie: Well hypothetically speaking, we could fit a bed in the basement.
杰森:太好了,这只是个假设而已.
Jason: Good thing that was a hypothetical question.
麦琪:杰森,你去是以为你想去呢,
Maggie: Jason are you going because you want to or because you're just
还是因为你想讨好我呢?
being nice to me.
杰森:亲爱的,得了吧,
Jason: Honey come on we've been married for twenty three years we don't
我们都结婚23年了,没必要互相讨好.
have to be nice to each other.
麦琪:杰森,那你为什么不待在家里.
Maggie: Jason why don't you just stay home.
杰森:好了,我说好了.
Jason: Alright I mean alright
迈克:哦,爸爸,你不想让妈妈一个人长途跋涉去旅游,对吗?
Mike: Ah dad you don't want mom to make that long trip all by her self do you?
杰森:别插嘴,迈克.
Jason: Don't help me here Mike.
迈克:不是,她可以带开萝尔去的.
Mike: No,but she could take Carol.
开萝尔:什么?
Carol: What?
本:求你了,求你了,求你了.
Ben: Please, please, please, please, please.
麦琪:哦,好吧,
Maggie: Oh come on Carol what do you say,
开萝尔你觉得怎么样,愿意陪老妈一起去吗?
you want to keep your old mom company?
开萝尔:哦,妈妈,我真的有很多的功课呢.
Carol: Well gee mom, I really have a lot of homework.
迈克:那好吧,
Mike: Well then sure Carol stay with us,
开萝尔可以跟我们在一起.
we'll stuff our faces together we'll watch three TV's and do our version
我们可以挤在一起看三个频道的电视并做波浪运动.
of the wave.
开萝尔:呃,我去.
Carol: Eww.
开萝尔:你说过这里每个人都很老.可这些人都…
Carol: I thought you said that everyone here was gonna be old.These people are all .
麦琪:对啊,这里怎么了?
Maggie: Firm, what's going on here?
开萝尔:这是青年周末的大聚会.
Carol: Twenty something meet and greet weekend.
麦琪:啊,怪不得每个人都这么年轻和健康.
Maggie: Aw that's why everyone here is so young and healthy.
开萝尔:丰田车都可以停到他们的胸大肌上.
Carol: With pecs you could park a Toyota on.
一个男人:听着,我一般只招呼扭捏走路的年轻娘们,
A man: You know I usually respond to the come hit the vibes a younger
但对你我决定破例了…我来了.
babes but in your case I have made an exception and hit the...I came.
麦琪:你难道不该去吞一只小老鼠去吗?
Maggie: Shouldn't you be digesting a small rodent?
男人:女士们,我吃过了,我愿意与你分享.
A man: You see Babes, I've got it and I would like to share it with you.
麦琪:在我不客气之前,你最好还是乖乖地给我走开.
Maggie: How would you like to walk away before I slam it in a window?
男人:真凶啊,你这个淘气的姑娘.
A man: You're kinky, you're a naughty girl.
麦琪:5,4…
Maggie: Five, four.
男人:好吧,但我是这里唯一跟你年龄相仿的人,
A man: Ok, ok but I'm the only one here who is almost your age,
现在不,那就回头见.
see me now or see me later.
麦琪:太好了,刚来就受到一个流球的侮辱.
Maggie: Great I've just been insulted by a walking oil sleek.
开萝尔:谢谢了,妈妈,早知道你把我拖到菜市场多好.
Carol: Thanks mom, mom I wish I knew you were dragging me to a meat market.
麦琪:对不起,亲爱的,我希望这不会扰乱你的学习.
Maggie: I'm sorry sweetheart, I hope this doesn't disturb your studying.
开萝尔:别提学习了.我的心都飞到家里去了.每个人呼喊着!
Carol: Forget studying, I left all my spandex at home.Everyone shouting!!!
迈克:噢!
Mike: Yeah
杰森:还有更精彩的吗,小伙子们?
Jason: Doesn't get any better than this, boys?
迈克:对好朋友们来说,今天是个特殊的日子.
Mike: Here's to good friends today is kind of special.
杰森:你可以尽情地施展自己的拿手好戏.
Jason: You gotta go for the gusto and bring out your best.
卢克:如果向空中吐痰,一定会落到你的脸上.
Luke: If you spit in the air it's gonna land in your face
杰森:卢克,生动的语言.
Jason: Words to live by Luke.
本:干脆把妈妈甩了得了,爸爸.
Ben: Smooth move you ditching mom, dad.
杰森:亲爱的,听我说.我非常爱你们的妈妈,珍惜我们一起度过的美好时光.如果没有她话,
Jason: Honey, listen just a second you know that I love your mother very much and I cherish the time we send together and I think we can all agree that this
你们也觉得这里少了点什么.
place is a little empty without her.
迈克:牙买加水上明星大赛什么时候开演?
Mike: So, what time are the Jamaican bob star trials?
卢克:看看记事板.
Luke: Let's go to the big board.
本:那好吧,半小时以后开始.我们必须在比基尼健美比赛和钓鱼比赛之间选择一个.等等,
Ben: Alright, Ok, they're in a half hour then we have to choose between the
bikini wikini contest and Fly casting withdrawal , wait a minute, how did that
怎么到这里了?
get on there.
迈克:是的,小伙子,这就是生活.
Mike: Yes my boys this is the life.
本:我多定了5个比萨.
Ben: I ordered five more pizzas.
迈克和卢克:太棒了.
Mike and Luke: Excellent.
罗杰斯护士:你好,西沃医生,我是格林威小学的罗杰斯护士.
Nurse Rogers: Hello, Dr.Sever I'm nurse Rogers from Greenway Elementary.
杰森:我知道,亲爱的,你回家干什么?你该在亨德森家里.我小女儿呢?
Jason: I know, sweetheart what are you doing home?You're supposed to be at the Henderson's how is my little baby?
罗杰斯护士:她长虱子了.
Nurse Rogers: She's got lice.
杰森:很好,虱子?
Jason: Okay, Lice?
罗杰斯护士:一种可怕的虱子,西沃医生.
Nurse Rogers: Pediculus Humanus Capitis, Dr.
就是那种有名的大头虱子.
Sever otherwise known as good old fashion head lice.
杰森:不,怎么会呢?
Jason: No no that can't be, that's impossible,
不可能的.我们家里里外外都收拾地很干净啊,大多数时候.
we keep an immaculate house around here, most of the times.
罗杰斯护士:是班里另一个孩子让她得上的.
Nurse Rogers: She got it from another child in her class,
最好的学校也发生了这样的事.
it happens in the finest schools,
我向你保证绝对没必要为此感到羞愧.
I assure you there is absolutely no shame involved in this.
杰森:羞愧?不,一点也不.我们没必要…
Jason: Shame?No, no certainly not at all we have to learn to.
男人:比萨来了.
Man: Hi there.
杰森:出去.
Jason: Get out.
罗杰斯护士:这不是什么严重的问题,只要你按照这些简单的说明去做就好了.
Nurse Rogers: Now this does not have to be a serious problem if you'll just follow these simple instructions.
杰森:好的,很好.
Jason: Yes alright.
罗杰斯护士:周末愉快.
Nurse Roberts: Have a nice weekend.
克莉丝:爸爸,我会好起来吗?
Chrissy: Daddy, Am I gonna be alright?
杰森:是的,别担心,我会好好照顾你的.
Jason: Yes come on, I'm gonna take good care of you.
迈克:我们必须用特制的去虱香波给她洗头发,还要把她头发里的每一个虱子都得抓下来;打扫家具,
Mike: Well, we have to wash her hair with a special lice shampoo and pick
off every single lice off every single strand of hair, vacuum the furniture,
scrub
擦洗地板,收拾床铺,清洗床单,最后把那些吃饱了的虱子封闭在塑料袋里.
the floors, strip the bed, wash the sheets, stick her stuffed animals in plastic bags
杰森:哇,哇,哇,哇.迈克,再说一遍,先做什么?
Jason: Wow wow wow wow Mike, start it over, what do we do first?
本:跟我们的周末吻别吧.
Ben: Kiss our weekend good bye.
麦琪:招待,
Maggie: Waiter, can you tell us if there is anything special going on
能告诉我们周末有什么特别的活动吗?
this weekend?
招待:我听说一些股票经纪人要来尽情喝啤酒,
Waiter: Well I heard some stock brokers are gonna drink as much beer as
然后为"1812叙诗"唱前奏.
they can and then burp the eighteen twelve overture.
开萝尔:我们想听听有什么集体活动.
Carol: We were thinking more along the line s of organized activities.
招待:哦,明天晚上有个大型舞会.
Waiter: Oh, well there's the big dance tomorrow night.
麦琪:哦,你爸爸不在,
Maggie: Ah, well it's just as well your father is not here,
我们过的也不错.有段时间他迷上了跳舞,不跳的肚子咕咕叫不停下来.
there was a time he used to do the hussles until his bell bottoms rang.
他们都叫他"星期六舞王".现在只有我骂他的时候,
They called him Saturday night Sever.
他才跳跳脚.
Now the only time he picks up his feet is when I bark him.
哦,那里有个年轻人一直在看你呢.
Oh, there's a young man over there that's looking at you.
开萝尔:我讨厌男孩子这么做.哦,妈妈,是哪个,哪个?
Carol: I hate it when guys do this, so come on mom, which one, which one?
麦琪:穿兰色高领的那个.他对你很感兴趣.
Maggie: The one in the blue turtle neck and he's definitely interested.
开萝尔:好吧,妈妈,我们设想一下,
Carol: Okay mom, let's say he's actually interested,
他对我感兴趣,把我带出去,
he takes me out and I have the time of my life in two weeks I'll
我们生活在一起.两周以后,我会坐在电话机旁,
be sitting by the phone power eating
吃着只用眼泪调味的烤干酪玉米片.
nachos seasoned only by the salt of my tears.
小伙子一:嗨,我叫布兰德,我…
Guy1: Hi I'm Brad and...
开萝尔:别乱叫,脏东西.
Carol: Buzz off scuzz bucket.
麦琪:哦,不,她在开玩笑呢.
Maggie: Oh no she's joking.
布兰德:你们是姐妹吗?
Brad: Are you sisters?
德怀特:我猜你是姐姐,你并不老,
Dwight: I guess you're the older one, not older more beautiful,
却更漂亮.不是说你不漂亮,但她是金发,
not that you're not beautiful but she is blond if it's real,
如果是真的话.我觉得是真的.
I think it's real.
对不起,我要回房间整理我的乱发去.
If you'll excuse me I think I'll go back to my room and re-spool
my floss
布兰德:他不经常出门.也许时机不太好,
Brad: he doesn't get out much, look maybe this is a bad time,
哦,我可以等会再约你吗?
well ah I'll catch you later?
开萝尔:也许可以,也许不可以.看看吧,我想要他.
Carol: Maybe maybe not we'll see, I want him.
机器:你后了,快点,你这个迟缓的人.
Machine: You are falling behind, come on slow poke.
麦琪:哦,算了吧,
Maggie: Oh, come on Carol let's try something else,
开萝尔,我们玩点别的吧.跟这种只会让你难堪的机器玩有什么意思啊.
it's no fun to work on a machine that can only insult you.
机器:跑的太好了,你真棒.
Machine: Excellent pace, you are amazing.
男人:嘿,美女,
Man: Hey puff cakes, you look a little winded,
你有点气喘,要不要我给你做人工呼吸?
how'd you like some mouth to mouth?
麦琪:离我远点,否则我就叫警察了.
Maggie: If you don't leave me alone, I'll have you arrested.
男人:哇,铐上我,
Man: Woo, cuff me frisk me and make me squeal,
搜我的身,打的我哇哇叫.我想还有10秒钟我栽了.
I'm thinking I got about ten seconds before I fell that,
我还是到安全的地方去吧,你可真凶.
so I'm gonna leave secure in the knowledge you dig me.
开萝尔:妈妈,你想试试划船机吗?
Carol: So mom, you want to try the rolling machine?
麦琪:只要不会说话的机器都可以.
Maggie: I'll try anything that doesn't talk.
开萝尔:我从没想到出一身大汗会这么好玩.啊,哦,天啊.
Carol: I've never realized how fun it was to build up a good clean sweat, Aw oh my gosh it's
布兰德:我很臭,我很讨厌,如果我不搭理他的话,他不会注意我的.
Brad I'm reek, I'm disgusting, maybe if I ignore him, he won't notice me.
布兰德:开萝尔,是吧?记得我吗,那个脏东西.
Brad: Carol, right, remember me, the scuzz bucket?
开萝尔:哦,对不起,
Carol: Aw I'm sorry,
我只是把你跟我认识的人给弄混了.
it's just that well I had you confused with every other guy I've ever met
布兰低:我们去游泳吧.
Brad: Spot me on some lap things.
开萝尔:我很乐意去.
Carol: I'll love to.
德怀特:嘿,我叫德怀特.
Dwight: Hi my name is Dwight.
麦琪:我叫麦琪.
Maggie: I'm Maggie.
德怀特:对昨天的事我很抱歉.遇到女人,我就结结巴巴的.
Dwight: Just wanted to apologize for yesterday I get kind of tongue tied around women
麦琪:啊.
Maggie: Aw.
德怀特:就是年轻姑娘.我不是说你老了.我是说你很老.
Dwight: You see young women, I mean not that you're old,
哦,我是说你很漂亮,但老了.
I mean you're pretty old, what I mean is you're pretty and old...
麦琪:德怀特…你就这么抱歉下去吗?
Maggie: Dwight...have we gotten to the apology part yet?
德怀特:对不起.你跟丈夫在一起吗?
Dwight: I'm sorry, so are you with you husband?
开萝尔:不,就我们俩.我们自由,毫无约束.
Carol: No, it's just us girls foot loose and fancy free.
德怀特:太好了.呃…
Dwight: Groovy, eh...
克莉丝:爸爸,你生我气了吗?
Chrissy: Daddy, are you mad at me?
杰森:不,你怎么这么说呢,亲爱的?
Jason: No, why would you say that sweet heart?
克莉丝:因为你老是发出跟你付帐时一样的声音.
Chrissy: Cause you're making the same noises you do when you pay bills.
杰森:好吧,我承认讨厌做这个,
Jason: Okay, I hate doing this but I love you and when we love somebody
但我爱你.当爱一个人的时候,
you'll do anything for them like comb lice eggs out of their hair,
你会为他任何的事,就像抓头发里的虱子卵拉,
help them with
帮他做功课了拉,去不爱去的地方拉,
their home work, go places we don't want to go,
做那些不爱做的事,比如跳舞.
do things we don't want to do like dancing.
克莉丝:你想跳舞吗?等我去录音机去.
Chrissy: You want to dance?Wait till I get my muffet's record.
杰森:不,不,等等,过来,
Jason: No no no wait, come here sweet heart,
亲爱的的.也许等会,我还要再检查几根头发呢.
maybe later I still got a few more hairs to cover.
克莉丝:我有多少根头发,爸爸?
Chrissy: How many hairs do I have daddy?
杰森:你有好几十亿根呢.
Jason: You have billions and billions.
卢克:我想我们还有40盆东西要洗呢.
Luke: I figure we got about forty loads of laundry left to do.
迈克:哦,如果我们把开萝尔的东西泡到汽油里烧了,就只有10盆了.
Mike: Well, only ten if we soak Carol's stuff in kerosene and torture it.
杰森:本不是也应该跟你们一起干吗?
Jason: Isn't Ben supposed to be helping you guys?
卢克:哦,他在楼上搞研究呢.他说要钻到虱子的脑袋里.
Luke: Ok, he's upstairs doing research, he said he is trying to get into the head of a louse.
迈克:他们可真是天生的一对.
Mike: which should be a comfortable fit.
杰森:嘿,本,下来,我们需要你.
Jason: Hey Ben come on down here we need you.
本:爸爸,我获得了很重要的信息,
Ben: Dad, I've got some really powerful information that's gonna save
会让我们省很多力气的.
us a lot of work.
杰森:是什么?
Jason: What's that?
本:鲸鱼,鸭嘴兽,犰狳不长虱子.
Ben: Whales, platapusses and armadillos don't get lice.
杰森:你把书放下,慢慢地退后.
Jason: I want you to put that book down and back away slowly.
本:多大的事啊?
Ben: What is the big deal?
算了吧,这不是谁的错,我们却把家给翻了个底朝天.如果是毒蜘蛛,
Come on this is not anybody's problem, we're turning the house upside down,
没说的,眼镜蛇,我也同意.
there were terangillas okay, cobras I'm right there with you but we're talking
但我们谈论的是虱子,它们只是让你皮肤痒而已.我一辈子都在痒.
about lice, so they make you itch, I've been itching my whole life.
杰森:这没什么好吹牛的,本.
Jason: That's nothing to brag about Ben.
迈克:该死,我教训他一下.
Mike: Damn it Gal let me just give it a shot I speak Ben,
我说,本,
now listen let's just say that one of these eggs hatches in this house
听着.假设有个虱子卵在咱们家孵化了,
and just one of these little
而且正好钻到你的头发里,我们正好在讨论虱子.好了,不久,人们就开始叫你虱子头了.
cooties jumps into your hair, we are talking lice capades.Alright then and petty soon people start calling you cootie head.
本:你们叫我的比这还差.
Ben: I've been called worst.
迈克:那么你就会从学校被打发回家了.
Mike: And then you get sent home from school.
本:太好了,放假了.
Ben: Great, vacation.
迈克:那么女孩都不会理你了.
Mike: And then no girl will ever date you.
本:我要找到那些虱子,杀死它们.
Ben: I want these lice found and I want them dead.
开萝尔:谢谢你坐过来,妈妈.
Carol: Thanks for sitting in with us mom,
我刚想和布兰德跳舞,
well Brad and I just wanted to dance and then we'll be stuck with Dwight
德怀特就过来纠缠,我被他纠缠.
and I'm stuck with, well you don't have
哦,那就没人陪你了.
anybody else either.
麦琪:哦,我希望大家都清楚,我来这只是吃东西.
Maggie: Well I hope that everybody understands that I am just here to eat.
布兰德:晚上好,女士们.
Brad: Evening Ladies.
开萝尔:嗨,布兰德.
Carol: Hi Brad.
布兰德:我特意采了这些花献给你.
Brad: I picked these out especially for you.
开萝尔:哦,妈妈,你看到过这么美丽的花吗?
Carol: Oh mom, have you ever since such beautiful flowers?
麦琪:事实上…
Maggie: Well as a matter of fact.
布兰德:开萝尔,想跳舞吗?
Brad: Carol, you wanna dance?
开萝尔:很乐意.
Carol: Love to.
麦琪:德怀特,这是什么?
Maggie: Dwight, what's this?
德怀特:花啊.
Dwight: Flowers.
麦琪:坐下,德怀特,我想我们得说清楚.
Maggie: Sit down Dwight, I think we have to clear something up.
德怀特:那好吧,我早该知道像你这么迷人的女人是不会看上我的.真笨,真笨,真笨.我花了15美元95美分.
Dwight: Great, I should have known an attractive woman like you wouldn't be interested in me, stupid, stupid, stupid, fifteen ninety five for the flowers,
干的好,德怀特,你都把价钱告诉她了,你还在自言自语.
nice going Dwight, you just told her how much they cost and you're talking
真笨,真笨,真笨.
to yourself, stupid, stupid, stupid.
麦琪:德怀特,别再打自己了.我想我们之间有个小误会.这不是约会.
Maggie: Dwight, quit beating yourself up, I think that there's just been a little misunderstanding here, this is not date.
德怀特:但我问开萝尔了,她说是的.
Dwight: But I ask Carol, she said yes.
麦琪:我说吃饭可以,但送花…柠檬?
Maggie: I said yes to dinner, not flowers and...lemon pledge?
德怀特:我走的太急了,太急了.我拿错东西了.
Dwight: I was in a hurry, I was in a hurry, I packed the wrong can.
麦琪:德怀特.我结婚了,而且很幸福.
Maggie: Dwight, I am a happily married woman.
德怀特:但在健身房里,你说你自由,毫无约束.
Dwight: But in the exercise room you said you were foot loose and fancy free.
麦琪:而你说好极了.
Maggie: And you said groovy.
德怀特:我盯上了一个已婚女人.看来我只好回到房间里去转我的鞋拔子了.再见.
Dwight: I just hit on a married woman, well the only thing left for me to do now is to go back to my room and rotate my shoe trees, see you.
麦琪:不,不,德怀特,坐下.这里全是跟你一样大的女孩,为什么不跟她们谈谈.
Maggie: No no no Dwight sit down, now there's a room full of girls your age why aren't you talking to them?
德怀特:我这个年龄的姑娘觉得我很闷.
Dwight: Girls my age don't find me exciting.
麦琪:那你跟她们试着说过了吗,
Maggie: Well have you ever tried talking to them the way you're talking
就像刚才跟我说的那样?
to me right now?
德怀特:我想,但做不到.我真希望像那些圆滑的主持人一样.
Dwight: I'll like to but I can't, just once I'll like to be one of those smooth operators who just walks up to anyone
他们可以走到任何人的面前,想说什么就说什么.
in the room and say exactly what's on his mind.
男人:嘿,宝贝,想舔我的乳头吗?
Man: Hey baby, you want to lick my nipples?
麦琪:不,我只想把它们揪下来.
Maggie: No, but I'll like to break them.
男人:如果不想和我跳舞,我就用叉子把眼睛挖出来.
Man: If you don't want to dance with me, I'll godge my eyes off with a cocktail fork.
麦琪:不好意思,我答应跟德怀特跳这支曲子了.给你.谢谢你帮我甩掉了那个家伙.你想跳多久我们就跳多久.
Maggie: Oh, I'm sorry I promised this dance to Dwight?But here.Thank you for getting me away from that guy.We can stop anytime you like.
男人:好的.
Man: Okay.
麦琪:你可以跳舞.
Maggie: You can dance.
男人:哦,是的.这只是常规锻炼.
Man: Well yeah this is just a regular PE.
卢克:我把所有的床单都洗了.床垫和弹簧床也收拾了.
Luke: I washed all the sheets vacuumed the mattresses and bock springs.
迈克:很好.
Mike: Good.
卢克:嘿,本呢?
Luke: Hey where's Ben?
迈克:我想他在楼上正在擦洗没拆下来的东西呢.
Mike: I think he is upstairs scrubbing everything that hasn't been nailed down.
迈克:啊,你认识本的时间比我长.我是说很高兴看到他干活这么卖力.但他总是这么头脑发热吗?
Luke: Ah, you've known Ben longer than I have, I mean I'm glad that he's
doing all the work but does he always get carried away like this
本:谁让你们停下来的?还有活儿没干完呢.
Ben: Who gave you guys the day off?There's work to be done.
迈克:橡胶人,求你饶了我们吧.我们快不行了.
Mike: Well have mercy on us rubber man, I think we're finished.
本:哦,真的?我说了才算呢.我们去记事板那去.死去的虱子旁边没有打记号.
Ben: Oh really?I'll be the judge of that, let's go to the big board, there's no check box next to stuffed animals.
卢克:我和迈克把它们放到塑料袋里了,要饿死它们.橡胶人.
Luke: Mike and I put them in plastic bags to starve the lice your rubberness.
本:这是什么,
Ben: What is this, some kind of joke to you guys?
你们在开玩笑吗?
This is my life here,
我的幸福都在这里呢.我在处理重大的健康危机,
I'm trying to deal with a major health crisis and I'm sure dad will back
我相信爸爸一定会支持我的.
me on this
杰森:本,把那个脱了吧,你看起来像浴缸塞子.
Jason: Ben, take off that outfit, you look like a bathtub stopper.
迈克:爸爸,你能告诉这个橡胶大王,活儿都干完了吗?
Mike: Dad come on will you tell the Lord of latex here that we're done.
本:对不起,爸爸.
Ben: I'm sorry dad but we are not done until the cootie board says,
只有记事板说完才能完.哦…我们干完了.
oooo we're done!
杰森:好的.我要出去.迈克,我要委托你负责其他的事.
Jason: Good, I'm going out, Mike I'm gonna leave you in charge of the others.
迈克:好的.我还高兴你总是先想到我,爸爸.
Mike: Okay, it's always nice to know I am your first choice dad.
杰森:不是的.开萝尔不在,而克莉丝又太小.
Jason: You weren't, Carol's out and Chrissy is too short.
迈克:你去哪?
Mike: Where are you going?
杰森:哦,我还有些没干完的工作.
Jason: Oh I have some unfinished business to take care of,
一,两个小时后,我给你们打电话.
I'll call you guys in a couple of hours.
迈克:好的,再见.
Mike: Okay, See yah.
杰森:再见.
Jason: Bye.
卢克:不知道你们想干什么,可我要看女子拔河比赛了.
Luke: I don't know about you guys but I'm watching the all girls tractor pudding.
本和迈克:好吧.
Ben and Mike: Alright.
迈克:克莉丝,你想干什么?
Mike: Chrissy, do you want anything done?
克莉丝:不干什么,布罗泛疃壬胍瞿汤胰髦巍?
Chrissy: Nothing's for Mr.Blow Hole as a cheeses sandwich.
迈克:什么先生?
Mike: Mr.who?
本:布罗先生跑到塑料袋外边干什么?
Ben: What's Mr.Blow Hole doing out of the plastic bag?
克莉丝:上午,我拿出来的.
Chrissy: I took him out this morning.
卢克:为什么?
Luke: You what?
克莉丝:你还记得吗?本说鲸鱼不长虱子.
Chrissy: Don't you remember?Ben said whales don't get lice.
迈克:克莉丝,克莉丝,
Mike: Chrissy Chrissy please tell me you didn't dray Mr.
说实话,你没带布罗先生到处乱转吧?
Blow Hole all over the house?
克莉丝:我没.
Chrissy: I didn't.
迈克:哦,谢天谢地.
Mike: Ah, Thank Goodness.
克莉丝:布罗先生害怕地下室.
Chrissy: Mr.Blow Hole was scared of the basement.
卢克:克莉丝!!!
Luke: Chrissy!!!
本:知道了.我们必须把整个家在打扫一遍.
Ben: That does it we have to clean the whole house all over again.
迈克:本,本,镇静.
Mike: Ben, Ben just stay calm.
本:我很镇静.
Ben: I am calm.
克莉丝:你还要用香波给我洗头发吗?
Chrissy: Do you have to shampoo my head again to?
迈克:没必要.
Mike: Not necessarily.
本:克莉丝,你想成为虱子老太婆吗?
Ben: Chrissy, how would you like to look like Shanado Corner?
开萝尔:真黑啊.
Carol: Kind of dark.
布兰德:是的,我从没晚上来这里过.
Brad: Yeah I've never been here in the night.
开萝尔:我希望不会遇到什么麻烦.
Carol: I hope we don't get in trouble.
布兰德:我已经遇到麻烦了.
Brad: I'm already in trouble.
机器:快点,迟缓的家伙.
Machine: Get moving slow poke.
布兰德:天啊,开萝尔,我以为是你呢,我们刚才干什么了?
Brad: My God carol I thought that was you, so where were we?
开萝尔:我们在亲吻.
Carol: We were kissing.
布兰德:是的.
Brad: Right.
开萝尔:我要走了.
Carol: And I was about to leave.
布兰德:为什么?我们相处的很好.
Brad: Why?We were getting along great.
开萝尔:不,一点都不好.是你好.
Carol: No we weren't, you were.
布兰德:我没怎么.
Brad: I don't get it.
开萝尔:我希望一个人亲我是真心的,而不是撒谎.
Carol: I need somebody who means it when he kisses me and doesn't lie.
布兰德:我什么时候撒谎了?
Brad: When did I lie?
开萝尔:你说从没来过这里,
Carol: You said you've never been in here before,
可你清楚地知道开关在哪里.
but you knew exactly where the lights were.
麦琪:来吧,德怀特,乐队又要演奏另一支曲子了.
Maggie: Come on Dwight the band's gonna play another one.
德怀特:麦琪,求你了.我不是年轻的时候了.
Dwight: Maggie please, I'm not as young as I used to be.
开萝尔:你俩真行啊.妈妈,你真棒.
Carol: You two are great.And Mom, you're amazing!
麦琪:哦,谢谢你宝贝.你看来也很开心啊.
Maggie: Oh thank you sweetheart and you seem pretty chirper yourself.
开萝尔:我为甩掉一个累赘而开心.
Carol: It feels so good to dump a hunk.
广播员:先生们,女士们,这是今晚最后一支曲子.
Announcer: Ladies and Gentlemen, it's the last dance of the evening .
麦琪:德怀特,你还有体力再陪我跳一个狐步舞吗?
Maggie: Dwight do you have enough strength for one more Fox Trout?
德怀特:我可以跳更多.
Dwight: South fill your harvest mood.
麦琪:我太吃惊了.
Maggie: surprise me.
杰森:我可以吗?
Jason: May I cut in.
麦琪:杰森,哦,亲爱的,你在这干什么?
Maggie: Jason,oh honey, what are you doing here?
杰森:吃完晚饭后,我心里涌出一个美好的渴望.
Jason: Well after we finished dinner I had a craving for something sweet.
麦琪:我的"周六舞王"又回来了?
Maggie: My Saturday Night Sever is back?
杰森:哦,你今晚与众不同,麦琪.
Jason: Oh Something different about you tonight Maggie.
麦琪:是吗?怎么了?
Maggie: There is?...What?
杰森:我不清楚,这是一种激情,
Jason: I don't know it's kind of a sort of a tingly, intense,
热烈,明亮的超级麦琪的形象.
light sort of super Maggie kinda thing.
麦琪:谢谢你.
Maggie: Thank you.
杰森:(唱歌)我越看你…
Jason: (sings) The more I see you.
麦琪:哦,真不相信你会过来.
Maggie: Oh, I can't believe you're here.
杰森:(唱歌)我越需要你.
Jason: (sings)The more I want you.
麦琪:你真好.天啊.
杰森:(唱歌)随着这种感情不断增长,你知道我唯一的爱人就是你.
00:22:21,100
Maggie: Praise you Jesus. Jason: (sings) And some how this feeling just grows and grows, you know the only one for me can only be you.